Evgeniya Makedonskaya

Phone: +972527952058

Email: jenn.mak@outlook.com Linked In: linkedin.com/in/janemak/

SUMMARY

I'm a business analyst with 6,5 years of experience in the software industry and 4,5 years of experience as business and system analyst. My focus area has been web applications in eCommerce. I'm looking for a role of senior **business and system (software) analyst**, ready to expand the area of responsibility into **product management role**.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Business Analyst Team Lead

Oct 2018 - Present

Mvideo-Eldorado, www.mvideo.ru, one of the biggest hardware stores in Russia

Responsibilities and Experience:

- created new version of the online store <u>www.mvideo.ru</u>, based on the microservices (as business analyst), all main pages of product selection process are in the pilot or production;
- built the analysis process from the scratch, created the site knowledge base;
- led the analyst team, expanded it from 2 to 27 members;
- was responsible for
 - reengineering and creating new business processes;
 - gathering and elaborations of different requirements: business, functional, non-functional, requirements for bff-level REST integrations;
 - supporting dev and QA teams during the entire feature life cycle;
 - estimating workloads and planning analyst tasks for product teams.

Business analyst

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

Gemotest laboratory, <u>www.gemotest.ru</u>,

Responsibilities and Experience:

- remodeled registration process;
- created and deployed to production the new algorithm for delivering patients results;
- created and deployed to production new payment process for cash registers and new process of fulfilling field orders day to day;
- was responsible for
 - reengineering business process;
 - business requirements elicitation, functional and non-functional requirements elaborations;
 - relational database design (using UML diagrams, SQL);
 - creating the interface (using Axure RP).

Junior software engineer

Jan 2016 - Jun 2017

TS consulting, tsconsulting.ru

Created the software, using Siebel eScript and JavaScript, SQL queries.

Junior QA automation engineer

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

Aplana Development Center, https://www.aplanadc.ru/

Responsibilities and Experience:

- developed Unit-tests, based on the acceptance criteria;
- resolved bugs identified as a result of testing.

EDUCATION

National Research Nuclear University MEPhI (Moscow Engineering Physics Institute)

- Master's degree, Computer Software Engineering (2015 – 2017, Graduated with honors)
- Bachelor's degree Applied Mathematics and Computer Science (2011 – 2015)

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- requirement elicitation and elaboration (business, functional, non-functional);
- BPMN:
- UML;
- REST API;
- SQL;
- user-story mapping;
- use case;
- agile (scrum, kanban);
- SEO in web applications.

Languages

English - fluent Russian - native German - basic (A1)

About me

In my free time I enjoy yacht racing, surfing, reading books and traveling.